A Guide to the Records of Western State Hospital, 1825-2000
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Administrative Records, 1825-2000., Extent: 77.75 cubic feet of records and 69 volumes.
  - Series I., Subseries E. DeJarnette Personal Files, 1906-1965.
    - Articles: Food Administrator, Staunton and Augusta County, 1918. (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - Articles: Gardening, 1936-1943; undated. (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - Articles: Hospital-related, undated. (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - Articles: Hot Room Treatment, undated. (Box 233, Folder 7)
    - Articles: Insulin Treatment, undated. (Box 233, Folder 8)
    - Articles: Liquor, 1938-1939; undated. (Box 233, Folder 9)
    - Articles: Miscellaneous, 1885-1955. (Box 233, Folder 10)
    - Articles: Nannette Hopkins, undated. (Box 233, Folder 11)
    - Article: "Syphilis as a Cause of Insanity," in The Virginia Medical Semi-Monthly, by Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1915. (Box 233, Folder 12)
    - Biographical Data (Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette), undated. (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Certificates, 1909-1938. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Certificates of Copyright Registration, 1943. (Box 233, Folder 13)
    - Christmas Cards, undated. (Box 233, Folder 14)
    - "Colonization of Inebriates," undated. (Box 243, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Mrs. Chertsey DeJarnette, 1906-1912. (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Mrs. Chertsey DeJarnette, 1916. (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Mrs. Chertsey DeJarnette, 1917. (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Mrs. Chertsey DeJarnette, 1917. (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Mrs. Chertsey DeJarnette, 1920-1928. (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Mrs. Chertsey DeJarnette, 1930-1937. (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Mrs. Chertsey DeJarnette, 1939-1940. (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Mrs. Chertsey DeJarnette, 1941. (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Mrs. Chertsey DeJarnette, 1942-1946. (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1906-1911. (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1912-1915. (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1916-1923. (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1925-1926. (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1927. (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1928. (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1928. (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1929. (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1930. (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1931-1932. (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1933-1935. (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1936-1937. (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1938-1939. (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1940. (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1941. (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1941. (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1942. (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1943. (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1943. (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1943. (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1943. (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1943. (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1943. (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1944. (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1944. (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1944. (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1944. (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, 1945-1952. (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette, undated. (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence/Documents: Orra Hopkins, 1920-1947. (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence/Documents: Orra Hopkins, 1957-1965l; undated. (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Court Papers (miscellaneous), 1926-1944; undated. (Box 233, Folder 15)
    - Death of Dr. Benjamin Hopkins (obituaries), 1916. (Box 233, Folder 16)
    - Deed, 1920. (Box 233, Folder 17)
    - DeJarnette Family Reunion, 1935. (Box 233, Folder 18)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary at Western State Hospital (Dr. J.S. DeJarnette), 1939. (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary at Western State Hospital (Dr. J.S. DeJarnette), 1939. (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary at Western State Hospital (Dr. J.S. DeJarnette), 1939. (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration Report, 1939. (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Tribute, 1939. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Harrison Antinarcotic Drug Act, 1912; undated. (Box 233, Folder 19)
    - Insurance Documents (DeJarnette Family), 1923-1925. (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Insurance Documents (DeJarnette Family), 1926-1927. (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Insurance Documents (DeJarnette Family), 1928-1933. (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Legislative Records and Editorials Regarding the Operation and Closure of DeJarnette State Sanatorium, 1932-1934. (Box 233, Folder 20)
    - Legislative Records Regarding Commitment, 1926. (Box 233, Folder 21)
    - Legislative Records Regarding Establishment of State Prison Farm for Misdemeanants, undated. (Box 233, Folder 22)
    - Memorial Resolutions for Daniel Coleman (Norfolk-Portsmouth Bar Association), 1935. (Box 233, Folder 23)
    - Newspaper articles, 1930. (Box 243, Folder 4)
    - "Our Prayer" (music and lyrics written by the DeJarnettes), 1943. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Paper dolls, undated. (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - Periodic Income Calendar (Orra Hopkins), 1957-1961. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Poetry, 1898-1949. (Box 233, Folder 24)
    - Poetry, 1950-1952. (Box 233, Folder 25)
    - Poetry, undated. (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - Poetry, undated. (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - Poetry, undated. (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - Poetry (Dr. Joseph S. DeJarnette), 1918-1934. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Poetry (Mrs. Chertsey DeJarnette), undated. (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - Poetry and Narratives, 1916-1922; undated. (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - Purchasers of Morphine at Elizabeth City, undated. (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - Religious Clippings, Writings and Pamphlets, 1885-1940. (Box 235, Folder 7)
    - Scrapbook: DeJarnette's Fiftieth Anniversary at Western State Hospital, 1939. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook: DeJarnette's Fiftieth Anniversary at Western State Hospital, 1939. (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Scrapbook: DeJarnette's Fiftieth Anniversary at Western State Hospital, 1939. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Scrapbook: DeJarnette's Fiftieth Anniversary at Western State Hospital, 1939. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Scrapbook: DeJarnette's Fiftieth Anniversary at Western State Hospital, 1939. (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Scrapbook: DeJarnette's Fiftieth Anniversary at Western State Hospital, 1939. (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Scrapbook: DeJarnette's Fiftieth Anniversary at Western State Hospital, 1939. (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Scrapbook: DeJarnette's Fiftieth Anniversary at Western State Hospital, 1939. (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Scrapbook: DeJarnette's Fiftieth Anniversary at Western State Hospital, 1939. (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Scrapbook: DeJarnette's Fiftieth Anniversary at Western State Hospital, 1939. (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Scrapbook: Miscellaneous Items, 1906-1956. (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Scrapbook: Miscellaneous Items, 1906-1956. (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Scrapbook: Miscellaneous Items, 1906-1956. (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Scrapbook: Miscellaneous Items, 1906-1956. (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Scrapbook: Miscellaneous Items, 1906-1956. (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Scrapbook: Miscellaneous Items, 1906-1956. (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Scrapbook: Miscellaneous Items, 1906-1956. (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Scrapbook: Miscellaneous Items, 1906-1956. (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook: Miscellaneous Items, 1906-1956. (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook: Miscellaneous Items, 1906-1956. (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook: Poetry, 1919-1952. (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook: Poetry, 1919-1952. (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook: Poetry, 1919-1952. (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Scrapbook: Poetry, 1919-1952. (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Scrapbook: Poetry, 1919-1952. (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Scrapbook: Poetry, 1919-1952. (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Scrapbook: Poetry, 1919-1952. (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Scrapbook: Poetry, 1919-1952. (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Scrapbook: Poetry, 1919-1952. (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Scrapbook: Poetry, 1919-1952. (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Scrapbook: Poetry, 1919-1952. (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Senate Bills, 1942; undated. (Box 235, Folder 8)
    - Shock Therapy in Treatment of Dementia Praecox and Manic Depressive Psychosis, undated. (Box 235, Folder 9)
    - Stock and Investments, 1928-1929. (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Stock and Investments, 1928-1929. (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Stock and Investments, 1928-1929. (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Stock and Investments, 1928-1929. (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Stock and Investments, 1928-1929. (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Stock and Investments, 1930-1935. (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Stock and Investments, 1937-1954. (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Tax Receipts, 1909-1916. (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Tax Receipts, 1917-1921. (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Tax Receipts, 1922-1929. (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Tax Receipts, 1930-1941. (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Tax Receipts, 1942-1947. (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Tennyson Birthday Book, undated. (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - "The Privately Owned Mental Sanatorium versus the State Owned Mental Sanatorium," undated. (Box 243, Folder 6)
    - "The Temperance Pledge," by Thomas F. Marshall, 1858 (copy), undated. (Box 235, Folder 10)
    - "The Virginia Challenge" (temperance publication featuring DeJarnette article), 1947. (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Wedding Invitation (Hopkins-DeJarnette), 1906. (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Series I., Subseries F. Employment and Personnel Records, 1915-1981.
    Contains ledgers and other material pertaining to employment and personnel activities. The absence ledger contains lists of male ward employees and what seem to be requests for days off from work. The Registration Books also document employee absences. The Employees Handbook contains helpful information for new employees. It covers pay, leave, retirement, and health insurance information, and provides descriptions of the duties performed by each department of the hospital. The Time Books contains monthly accounts of work attendance by each ward's regular attendants. This book accounts for male ward employees only. The three later volumes contain what appear to be monthly accounts of work attendance by those employed in the business office. The Weekend Book contains several miscellaneous sections of notes and short entries about weekend personnel activities, followed by a list of nurse supervising duties and a list of representative meetings. The telephone directories contain at-work contact information for employees of Western State, as well as numbers for general and designated work areas. The records in this series are part of accession 41404.
    Arranged alphabetically.
    - Absence Register, 1935-1937. (Volume 32)
    - Employee Handbook (2 copies), undated. (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Employment Applications and Letters, 1923-1982. (Box 232, Folder 30)
    - Employment History Form, 1938. (Box 232, Folder 31)
    - Nursing Duties, Essays on, 1915; undated. (Box 232, Folder 32)
    - Registration Book, 1926-1932. (Volume 33)
    - Registration Book, 1926-1933. (Volume 34)
    - Telephone Directory, 1971. (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Telephone Directory, 1974. (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Telephone Directory, 1981. (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Time Book (Ward Attendants), 1933-1934. (Volume 35)
    - Time Book (Business Office), 1961-1963. (Volume 36)
    - Time Book (Business Office), 1963-1965. (Volume 37)
    - Time Book (Business Office), 1965-1967. (Volume 38)
    - Weekend Book, 1969-1980. (Volume 39)
  - Series I., Subseries G. Executive Committee Records, 1841-1903.
    Contains four volumes of Executive Committee meeting minutes and information about committee activities. The Executive Committee was composed of a small number of members of the Western State Court of Directors (Board of Directors). The committee met on a monthly basis and was responsible for reviewing the superintendent's reports, auditing the steward's monthly expense accounts, and overseeing other matters that arose between Board meetings. For additional information about the Board of Directors and its duties, please see Series I. Administrative Records, Subseries B. Board of Directors Records. For reports of the Executive Committee, please see Series I. Administrative Records, Subseries N. Reports. The Executive Committee records are part of accession 41404.
    - 1841-1878. (Volume 40)
    - 1878-1884. (Volume 41)
    - 1884-1897. (Volume 42)
    - 1898-1903. (Volume 43)
  - Series I., Subseries H. General Files and Ledgers, 1828-1997.
    Contains subject and miscellanous files found throughout the Western State Hosptial collection. The files consist of a variety of material including limited correspondence, memos, working papers, and other related documents pertaining to a particular subject or person. The files were most likely maintained by the hospital superintendent or his office staff, but in some cases the origin is unknown. Many files contain only one document, while other subjects fill several folders. The title of "General Files" was given in order to encompass all of the subject files, as well as lone and/or miscellaenous documents found in the collection. These files are part of accessions 31030, 31353, 31704, and 41404.
    The files are separated by the century in which they were created, and then alphabetically within.
    - 19th Century Files, 1828-1893.
      Contains miscellaneous files and individual documents found in various parts of the Western State Hospital collection. Much of the earlier material was found mixed in with the superintendent's correspondence. Topics of note include the 1883 patient poisonings and the subsequent investigation performed by the Pinkerton company, the handwritten job descriptions, including those for the ten pin alley attendant, the night nurse, and the steward, as well as the files of legal documents that include wills, estate settlements, and summonses. Researchers should note that additional 19th century files (1828-1873) can be found in Series VI. Records Found at Eastern State Hospital (Accesion 44812).
      Arranged alphabetically by subject or document type.
      - Admissions and Monetary Disbursements, 1828-1869. (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Applications for Discharge, 1869-1877. (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Bills and Receipts, 1829-1856. (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Bills and Receipts, 1859-1879. (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Blackburn's Trip to Examine Other Hospitals (Thomas Blackburn), 1854. (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Blank Forms (misc.), undated, circa 1850-1880. (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Chemistry notebook, undated. (Volume 1043)
      - Clothing Furnished, 1832-1864. (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - Clothing Slips and Receipts, 1846-1867. (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Clothing Slips and Receipts, 1868-1876. (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - Contracts and Agreements, 1836-1849. (Box 78, Folder 10)
      - Contracts and Agreements, 1852-1872. (Box 78, Folder 11)
      - Hair and Eye Color Survey, 1850. (Box 78, Folder 12)
      - Images of Western State Hospital (Western Lunatic Asylum), 1828-1893. (Box 78, Folder 13)
      - Inventories (misc.), 1834-1865. (Box 78, Folder 14)
      - Job Descriptions, 1853; undated. (Box 78, Folder 15)
      - Legal Documents (misc.), 1846-1856. (Box 78, Folder 16)
      - Legal Documents (misc.), 1860-1890. (Box 78, Folder 17)
      - Meal Plans (Bills of Fare), 1840-1860. (Box 78, Folder 18)
      - Memos (misc.), 1855-1877. (Box 78, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous Documents, 1841-1889; undated. (Box 78, Folder 20)
      - Newspaper Clippings, undated, circa 1860-1880. (Box 78, Folder 21)
      - Notes About Patients, 1840-1867. (Box 78, Folder 22)
      - Notes About Patients, 1868-1873; undated. (Box 78, Folder 23)
      - Obligation Bonds, 1850-1876. (Box 78, Folder 24)
      - Patient Census Information, 1887. (Box 78, Folder 25)
      - Patient Poisonings: Coroner's Inquest, 1883. (Box 78, Folder 26)
      - Patient Poisonings: Coroner's Inquest, 1883. (Box 78, Folder 27)
      - Patient Poisonings: Pinkerton Investigation Correspondence, 1883. (Box 78, Folder 28)
      - Patient Poisonings: Pinkerton Investigation Reports, 1883. (Box 78, Folder 29)
      - Patient Poisonings: Pinkerton Investigation Reports, 1883. (Box 78, Folder 30)
      - Patient Poisonings: Pinkerton Investigation Reports, 1883. (Box 78, Folder 31)
      - Patient Poisonings: Pinkerton Investigation Reports, 1883. (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Patient Poisonings: Proceedings of the Committee of Investigation of the Legislature of Virginia, 1883. (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Pledges, 1862-1874. (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Receipts for Patients Delivered to Western State Hospital, 1850-1851; undated. (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - Recipes for Medicine, 1857-1872. (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - Senate Bill 93: Transportation of Convicts and Insane Persons, 1878. (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - Slaughterhouse / Butcher, 1851. (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - Statistical Information About Activities, 1857. (Box 79, Folder 8)
      - Steward's Financial Estimates, 1856. (Box 79, Folder 9)
      - Stribling, Dr. Francis T., Obituaries, 1874. (Box 79, Folder 10)
      - Superintendent's Ledger (misc.): Discharge Requirements / Disease Definitions, 1880-1886. (Volume 44)
      - Superintendent's Ledger (misc.): Lists of Institutions for the Insane, undated; circa 1866. (Volume 45)
      - U.S. Naval Hospital, Portsmouth, Virginia: Table of Insane Persons, 1848. (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - 20th Century Files, 1907-1997, (bulk 1960-1980).
      Restricted: Documents containing patient names and information that are less than 125 years old. Some records may require review by an archivist and/or redaction (if it is possible) before they are served. Contains subject and correspondence files which most likely originated in the office of the hospital superintendent. Files of note include those related to the hospital's growing geriatric program, its commitment to industrial therapy and vocational rehabilitation, as well as correspondence between the superintendent and the Virginia Attorney General, and Superintendent of Hospitals, William S. Allerton. Additional information on the Shenandoah Geriatric Treatment Center or the Community Hospital Industrial Rehabilitation Program (CHIRP)can be found Series II. Departmental and Program Records. Many of the 20th Century Files (mostly post-1945) were originally known as "Director's Correspondence and Reference Files."
      Arranged alphabetically by subject or correspondent.
      - Achievement Awards Competition (American Psychiatric Association), 1968-1970. (Box 79, Folder 12)
      - Adolescent Unit, 1974-1975. (Box 79, Folder 13)
      - Adolescent Unit, 1975. (Box 79, Folder 14)
      - Adolescent Unit, 1976. (Box 79, Folder 15)
      - Adolescent Unit, 1976. (Box 79, Folder 16)
      - Allerton, William S., 1967-1969. (Box 79, Folder 17)
      - Allerton, William S., 1970. (Box 79, Folder 18)
      - Allerton, William S., 1970. (Box 79, Folder 19)
      - Allerton, William S., 1971. (Box 79, Folder 20)
      - Allerton, William S., 1971. (Box 79, Folder 21)
      - Allerton, William S., 1972. (Box 79, Folder 22)
      - Allerton, William S., 1972. (Box 79, Folder 23)
      - Allerton, William S., 1972. (Box 79, Folder 24)
      - Allerton, William S., 1973. (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Allerton, William S., 1973. (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Allerton, William S., 1973. (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - Allerton, William S., 1974. (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - Allerton, William S., 1974. (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - Allerton, William S., 1975. (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Allerton, William S., 1975. (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - Allerton, William S., 1976. (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - Allerton, William S., 1976. (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - Allerton, William S., 1976. (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - American Hospital Association Surveys, 1947-1953. (Box 80, Folder 11)
      - American Hospital Association Surveys, 1956-1959. (Box 80, Folder 12)
      - American Hospital Association Surveys, 1960-1962. (Box 80, Folder 13)
      - American Hospital Association Surveys, 1963-1967. (Box 80, Folder 14)
      - American Hospital Association Surveys, 1968-1969. (Box 80, Folder 15)
      - American Hospital Association Surveys, 1970-1972. (Box 80, Folder 16)
      - American Hospital Association Surveys, 1973-1974. (Box 80, Folder 17)
      - American Hospital Association Surveys, 1975-1976. (Box 80, Folder 18)
      - American Hospital Association Surveys, 1976-1977. (Box 80, Folder 19)
      - Anniversary (160th), 1988. (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Archives / Archives Committee, Establishment of, 1976-1977. (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - Articles and Speeches (Western State Hospital related), 1916-circa 1950. (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - Articles and Speeches (Western State Hospital related), 1967. (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - Articles and Speeches (Western State Hospital related), 1969-circa 1981. (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Association of Medical Superintendents of American Institutions for the Insane Poster, undated. (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Attorney General, 1962-1970. (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Attorney General, 1971. (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - Attorney General, 1972. (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - Attorney General, 1973. (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - Attorney General, 1974. (Box 81, Folder 10)
      - Attorney General, 1974. (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - Attorney General, 1975-1976. (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - Attorney General, 1976. (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - Attorney General, 1976. (Box 81, Folder 14)
      - "Beautiful Thornrose" book, 1921. (Volume 1042)
      - Blotters and Bookmarks, undated. (Box 81, Folder 15)
      - Blotters and Bookmarks, undated. (Box 81, Folder 16)
      - Brochure (Western State Hospital), 1975. (Box 81, Folder 17)
      - Budget Advisory Tours (Capital Outlay), 1959-1968. (Box 81, Folder 18)
      - Budget Advisory Tours (Capital Outlay), 1969-1971. (Box 81, Folder 19)
      - Budget Advisory Tours (Capital Outlay), 1971-1973. (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Budget Advisory Tours (Capital Outlay), undated. (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Budget Advisory Tours (Capital Outlay), undated. (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Census Reduction, 1972. (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Census Reduction, 1972. (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Census Reduction, 1972-1973. (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Centennial Celebration speech, 1928. (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Certificates (misc.), 1945-1988. (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - Checklist for Analyzing a Situation in Order to Change It, undated. (Box 232, Folder 1)
      - Chemistry Examination, undated. (Box 232, Folder 2)
      - Civil Rights, 1964-1969. (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - Civil Rights, 1971-1972. (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - Civil Rights, 1973. (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - Civil Rights, 1973-1974. (Box 82, Folder 12)
      - Coal Report Forms (blank), 1918. (Box 82, Folder 13)
      - Competency (State Board Regulation #9), 1964-1980. (Box 82, Folder 14)
      - DeJarnette / Hopkins Marriage Story, 1976. (Box 82, Folder 15)